Don't attract too much attention.
Okay.
Yah!
I'll be back!
Prince Renato and I were engaged,
so I returned to my home
in the Kingdom of Muro.
Always a Catch!
Knight Captain
Episode 5
How the One That Got Away Visited Home
It takes three days to travel from
the royal capital in Rubini to Muro.
First, I'd take the Ametis family
carriage to a town near the border,
where I'd transfer to a carriage
sent by the Annovazzis to pick me up.
This place looks fun.
L-Lady Maria, please don't
wander around too much.
It'll be fine. Besides, we've
got time until my ride arrives.
Good grief.
These were just picked
this morning. Try one.
They're delicious.
I wish Prince Renato could try these.
He eats fine meals every day, but
I doubt he gets much freshly-picked fruit.
Here.
That can wait until after
we're married... I guess.
Care for some grapes, milady?
Grapes? Yes, please.
Th-The sweetness and sourness
are perfectly balanced,
and a rich aftertaste
spreads throughout my mouth!
I know, right?
For a limited time, I'm selling
all you can fit in one basket.
Sold!
Milady!
You can instantly tell
they were sent by my family.
Goffredo, Macchio!
Milady.
It's good to see you again.
You seem well.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Hey, crown princess!
We're relieved you
haven't changed, milady!
Seriously? Please.
We're still only engaged.
FREEZE
That's right.
Crown princess.
What is the meaning of this?
The whole house was in a panic
after receiving that letter
from the King of Rubini!
Was Dad angry?
We don't know.
We've never seen him make
that face before either.
What?
What about my sisters?
Even your married sisters have
returned and are waiting for you.
Ugh...
I won't have any peace. I'm not
sure I want to go home anymore.
Now, now.
You must explain what happened yourself.
Oh. Little Lord Teodorico said,
"I can't wait to see my sister again."
Okay, I'll be right there!
Thank you! Goodbye!
You must be exhausted from the long
journey, but we'll only stop for lunch.
We'd like to cross the border
sooner rather than later.
Okay.
Is that a noble lady?
What's she doing out here?
Have you gotten used to life in Rubini?
Yes. It's so much fun.
Everyone's so kind to me.
That's good.
Thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
This is delicious.
Maybe it's because we're near Muro,
but this food tastes like back home.
Do Muro and Rubini dishes taste different?
Well, they're similar,
but Rubini dishes aren't
as strongly flavored.
Are you all right eating that much?
You become a bottomless pit
when you're hungry.
Hey, that's rude.
You haven't changed a bit.
Really? I think I've gotten
a bit more ladylike.
You must be joking.
Definitely not.
What's your problem?
Recently, the mountain road
to the Kingdom of Muro
has become dangerous
due to bandit attacks...
That must be around here.
Nothing happened when I came
through here six months ago.
Either way, it's only been six months,
but it feels so long ago.
I guess I've been dealing with a lot.
My grapes...
What's wrong?
Forgive me, milady. It's just...
If you want to pass,
you'll have to beat us first!
What?
What's going on? Are they the bandits?
I'll convince them to let us through.
Please wait inside.
They don't look like bandits.
Try to settle this peacefully.
That will depend on how they respond.
What seems to be the problem?
Who are you people?
Forgive us, milord! Please arrest us
and take us to the royal castle!
Please!
Please, sir!
Huh?
What?
What's going on?
Ah, a noble lady.
She must be a lady.
She's a lady fer shore.
Please, milady.
They're all armed with
well-maintained farming tools.
They must use these for work.
I don't sense any bloodlust either.
They don't seem to be trying to trick us.
We'll at least hear you
out. Raise your heads.
What a kind lady.
This might actually work.
We're real lucky fer shore.
One of you has quite the heavy accent.
I don't know why you're doing this,
but you should choose your
victims more carefully.
You shouldn't attack carriages
driven by such muscular men.
We're terribly sorry.
But the chief's daughter's gone missing
from our village of Navarro.
Missing?
Yes. She suddenly
disappeared a few days ago.
We've visited the local lord's mansion
several times, but he's ignoring us.
Who's the lord of this area?
Count Nardi.
I've never met him.
The guards and knights
won't investigate without him.
What kind of terrible lord ignores
his people when they're in need?
STOMP
Perhaps I'll pay him a visit.
Please don't, milady.
STOMP
I can't believe him.
You'd only be causing trouble for Prince
Renato by going to visit the count.
His people need his help.
STOMP
Let's hear everything
they have to say first.
So you attacked a noble's carriage
so you'd be arrested
and taken to the royal castle?
Yes. We thought we'd be able to
speak to the head of the guards.
We're sorry, but we had no other choice.
Why is everyone in this kingdom
so self-sacrificing?
You called?
Here.
I don't know if this'll help right away,
but go to the royal castle and show
this to the soldiers at the gate.
If all goes well, the crown prince's aide
Raimondo, will help you... probably.
He works quickly, and he's a good person.
Though he can be disagreeable.
Did you say something, milady?
You know the crown prince?
You could say that.
Thank you, milady.
Thank you.
How can we thank you?
Just don't do anything
reckless like this again.
We won't.
There are good people in the world, too.
We're proud to say
that kind girl's from our town.
We'll do our best
to get them to look for her.
I hope it goes well.
Sounds like more trouble.
Seriously? What now?
It came from over there.
Let's go.
What a haul!
Carriages headed to the capital
are packed with nice stuff!
We got lucky with this one, boss.
Check this out.
This is nice meat.
Someone carry this.
Transporting nobles' goods without guards
is asking to be robbed.
Wow, they're the very picture of bandits.
This is no time to be impressed.
What should I do?
Now that I've seen them...
Yes?
You're here?
I know. I've got an idea.
FANFARE!
This can't be good.
It's a great plan.
That carriage serves nobles
in the capital, doesn't it?
Yes, as they just considerately explained.
Bring tools to repair
the carriage from your village.
If they're indebted to you, that might
get the guards to act more quickly.
But we can't reach the village
without going that way.
What? Really?
Take that over there.
We can't chase off
those terrifying bandits.
Don't worry.
We'll handle them.
Always a Catch!
I hope Mimi reached
the Kingdom of Muro safely.
Don't worry.
I reminded Lady Maria to avoid
sticking her nose in danger
no matter what happens.
Thanks.
Will they be all right?
Why is she going with them?
It sounded like only
the strongmen would be fighting.
Here's the plan, milady.
Macchio and I will surround
the carriage and talk to them.
If they don't listen, we'll take
them down one by one. That's it.
What should I do?
Please hide here, milady.
What? Why?
A lady fighting in a dress
would draw too much attention.
Weren't you told to stay out of trouble?
Under no circumstances!
Aw, fine. I'll watch for anyone
who might try to flee.
Don't worry about that.
Let's go, Goffredo.
Yeah.
Who are you guys?
Stop what you're doing, or else...
We'll hit you.
They're terrible negotiators.
Well, it's not like
they'll be overpowered.
Wait, are they just
testing their abilities?
Just watching is no fun.
SNEAK...
30!
Honestly.
Don't worry? They let one get away.
Hey, I found one over here.
DRAG DRAG
Milady! We told you to stay hidden.
Boss...
You'll pay for that!
TAP
That's a weak point known
as Benkei's weakness.
Long ago, a giant man named Benkei
had his entire body shot
full of arrows, and...
That doesn't make sense!
Where did the arrows come from?
You fell for it, fool.
I pretended to be unconscious
so you'd let your guard down.
If you don't want the girl
to get hurt, don't move.
Now you can't do anything.
I'm going to take my time tormenting you.
Boss!
Milady!
Watch out!
All scoundrels think the same, huh?
38!
Th-They're monsters!
Run!
What wimps.
Prince Renato wasn't blown away.
What? Really?
You used your 38 on Prince Renato?
Was he all right?
Shall I get you a coat?
No, I'm fine.
In the East, they say sneezes are
caused by people speaking about you.
Perhaps Mimi is telling someone about me.
You saved me. Thank you.
That was almost a disaster.
You should hire guards next time.
We reattached your wheels.
If you drive slowly, you can
make it to the nearby village
and get proper repairs done there.
I believe it's called Navarro Village.
The villagers there are
famous for their kindness.
I don't know how to
thank you for everything.
Have a pleasant trip.
Wait. What are your names?
Our names aren't worth mentioning.
It's so pretty. Navarro Village
is around there, isn't it?
Yes. We're almost at the border.
I wonder if those villagers have
already left for the capital.
I hope it goes well for them.
You really haven't changed, milady.
You think so?
Maybe you're right.
I'm finally back in Muro.
Could you stop the carriage
once we're inside the gates?
I'd like to walk around
since it's been a while.
Yes, milady.
I'm so used to Aida's mansion
that this place feels unfamiliar
even though I grew up here.
This smell brings back memories.
It's like being wrapped up
in a warm blanket.
Eight!
I'm home.
Translation: Sho Stifler
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Alicia Ashby
Quality Control: Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control: Michelle Tymon
I have four older sisters.
You bet they all listen to me
since I'm a skilled martial artist?
Well, you'd be wrong.
WHACK WHACK THUD THUD POW
My sisters are scary when
they're mad, especially...
Next Time
How the One That Got Away Fought With Her Father
I spoke my mind again, but
I stopped myself in time.